Hey there, and welcome to these lessons on programming in Python.
在那里 欢迎使用 Python 中的编程
We're glad to have you with us.
很高兴你和我们一起
In this course, you will be writing programs in the Python programming language.
在此课程中 您将以 Python 编程语言编写程序
There are many programming languages in the world today but Python is one that has
当今世界有很多编程语言 但 Python 是有
a great reputation for being both easy to learn and very practical.
既容易学习又很实用
Python code can run on any major kind of computer today.
Python 代码今天可以在任何主要的计算机上运行
From a Windows PC or a Mac to a high-powered Linux server or even on
从 Windows PC 或 Mac 到高性能 Linux 服务器甚至是
your phone and Python is used in all sorts of fields
你的手机和 Python 都用在各种领域
from Web development to data analysis to artificial intelligence.
从 Web 开发到数据分析到人工智能
The skills you'll learn here are central to your journey to becoming a programmer.
你在这里学到的技能是你成为程序员的中心
Many of the concepts you'll learn in these lessons are not limited to Python.
您在这些课程中学习的许多概念并不仅限于 Python
We'll go over some of the most fundamental building blocks of programming, ideas,
我们将会进行一些最基本的编程 想法
and skills that will be useful for you no matter
和对你有用的技能
what area of programming you're interested in pursuing.
你感兴趣的节目领域
In the next few lessons,
在接下来的几课中
the programs you'll work on use a feature called Turtle Graphics.
您将使用名为 Turtle Graphics的功能部件
The turtle is an imaginary robot that can draw colorful shapes on the screen.
乌龟是一种假想的机器人 可以在屏幕上画出彩色的形状
This way, you can quickly tell what your programs are doing.
这样 你就可以快速讲述你的节目在做什么
Learning to code is only partly about learning
学习代码只是部分学习
the grammar of a programming language such as Python.
编程语言的语法 如 Python
It's mostly about learning a way of thinking about patterns, repetition,
它主要是关于学习一种思维模式 重复
processes, and information and the Turtle gives us a way to visualize that.
过程 信息和 Turtle 给了我们一个可视化的方式